for this group where man, we start off,
you feel like you're getting a little
bit of momentum. I make a terrible third
down and one call. No excuse for that.
Should have used the timeout. They did a
good job of of uh you know, having a
good call on there and then we got to
punt it out. And I thought our defense,
you know, they just made them snap it
one more time. It looked like they were
getting themselves close to field goal
range. And what a freaking play by Cam
Curl. I thought our defense came up time
in and timeout tonight. Um and then
offensively to be able to make those
plays, to be able to get back into field
goal range, I thought was big. I thought
Matthew did a great job of finding KBY
early in that drive to be able to get up
the sidelines for the first first down.
Devonte makes an unbelievable catch on
the sideline and then I thought the
third and six conversion that Nua had.
We took the timeout, didn't like the
look. Uh Matthew finds him and he's so
strong and um and then we were able to
get a few more yards and then Meas
punches it in and so uh hell of a deal
right there. But uh a lot that we can
learn from, you know, I'm I'm just
really proud of this football team and
the resolve. It's it's served us well. I
think we've needed that in each of the
last two games and we'll have to be
better if we expect to be able to you
know come away with the result we want
against a you know a special football
team next week but we're excited to get
a chance back at Lumen.
>> It's been a crazy journey for you guys
with field goals this season.
>> So what's it like to think about this
game coming down to that and how did it
feel to see it go through I
>> I felt really confident Nate you know I
mean obviously since has been in there
and really you know you talk about Jake
and Ethan I think that whole operation
has been really good. We obviously only
had the one miss that that was at Philly
or I mean at Seattle the last time we
played him on that Thursday night. But
um a lot of confidence in him and it was
nice too because it felt like it was
like all right the football gods are
smiling on us. The weather had calmed
down. There wasn't a lot of wind right
there. And so I said uh after that
fourth down conversion, can you guys
believe they made that play right there?
I mean that was unbelievable to uh man
I'm up here by myself, huh? You guys
aren't even participating at all. But I
just I I was really happy for him Nate
and and I was very confident that he
would make that. tough was it when Caleb
makes that crazy play to send it to over
time.
>> Yeah, you know what? It was tough, but I
thought what was great is is hey, we
can't do anything about it. Go on to the
next play. Here we are in overtime. What
what happened then is is done with. And
we always talk about being in the
moment, being totally and completely
present. And I thought our guys did a
great job of that. And you know, I was
really kicking myself because I felt
like when we possessed the ball first,
and I had mentioned it, I thought that
possession was going to really cost us.
And there's no excuse for that. You
know, I have to be better for our group.
I will be better for our group. Uh but
man, I just can't say enough about the
defense, uh what they did, and then for
Cam Curl to be able to make that play.
What a freaking catch. Um you know, and
then offensively for those guys to do
what they did to be able to go get in
field goal position and um you know,
when we had some chances, I thought we
were going to be able to get a walk-off
there with Kobe or Ferg, but uh you
know, it didn't work out and then Meas
uh ended up making it true and here we
are. And uh excited to be able to get a
chance to work again. you tell Matthew
uh Matthew before the pass to Nakula uh
during the timeout.
>> Yeah, I just I was we were really
talking about what play we liked, you
know, because I had taken the timeout.
They had shown, you know, some similar
structures defensively and we had had
some success with that particular
concept and um and he did a great job
being able to execute it. So, just
telling him what what my thoughts were.
I changed the play call from what the
previous one was and just kind of
explaining the thought process and he
did a great job bringing it to life.
What did you think about the Cam Curl
and Kobe Durant had?
>> I thought they were awesome. You know, I
mean, Kobe makes a, you know, a bunch of
plays earlier in the game. Um, you know,
wish we would have capitalized on the
one pick that he did make. We end up
going three and out right there. That
was, you know, not good complimentary
football. And again, I I'm I'm really
excited because I can dive into this and
I can be better for us. And we'll have
to be against a phenomenal defense next
week. But guys just kept battling. They
kept believing. Um, and that's what it's
about. You know, there's no style
points. It's about being able to survive
in advance and we were able to do that
in a tough hostile environment and it
was cold as today.
>> When we left the field in Seattle last
time,
>> did you have a feeling you guys meeting?
>> We were hopeful. You know, I I I you
know, once those guys won u you know, I
I I was hoping that we'd get a chance to
be able to go back and um you know,
thought this would be a scenario that
could possibly set itself up and and
here we are.
>> Last time you guys played the Super
Bowl, you know, you guys built a team a
certain way. uh you know to be able to
get back here doing it an entirely
different way. Uh I don't know what is
what have you learned I guess about the
>> that it's all about people you know and
um you know I love this team. I love the
the makeup of this group you know top to
bottom. We got some veteran guys on
offense. We're relatively young on
defense. Um I think we've done a good
job of being able to acquire a bunch of
different you know using the different
avenues that you can use to be able to
acquire players. But it's about the
people. You know I I think we're getting
better. I can't say enough about how
much I love working for Mr. Kroni, how
much I love leading alongside Les,
Kevin, and Tony, and really our coaching
staff and being able to identify guys
that bring this stuff to life and that
are that have that uh character, the
competency, and you know, just the
overall competitiveness and competitive
stamina that was needed tonight. So,
happy for them. We got another step next
week, though. And uh I know uh we're
excited to be able to advance, but we're
not satisfied. And uh these guys have
high standards, and we got to be at our
best. Uh you know, you watched that game
last night, they're firing on all
cylinders. They look really good. And uh
you know I'm excited to be able to dive
into this tape and figure out how we can
improve.
>> Couple more guys.
>> You [snorts] guys rebuilt this team um
to potentially be on the road in the
elements to run the ball phys be
physical and pose your will. Um is there
anything to take from tonight going so
pass heavy in the elements against a
really good DBs group?
>> Yeah. You know what I think what I I
kind of mentioned it. I could have done
a much better job. And then I did think
once we were able to get some success,
we settled into a little bit of a
different approach, you know, being able
to lean on the run and then when we were
throwing it, um, picking up the tempo a
little bit and I thought Matthew had a
bunch of success keeping the ball in
play and guys made their plays. And so,
um, I think overall what I would say,
Jordan, is I did not like the feel for
the flow of the game that I had outside
of the first, you know, series where our
guys did a great job defensively it kept
us in it in spite of how, you know,
poorly, you know, poor of a job I did
for our group. Um, but like I said, you
know, I'm I'm really grateful for this
group being able to find a way, stick
with it, um, and be able to overcome
some bad coaching by me tonight.
You got a game a [snorts] month ago
where you go to Seattle, you're up by 16
points, it gets away. It's a It's a game
that I'm sure naws at you. Now you have
this opportunity to go back up there.
You earn your way back. What does it
mean to you? What does it mean to the
team to get to go back up there and try
to write that wrong?
>> Yeah, it means that we've got an
opportunity to be totally present, have
a great week of preparation, uh learn
from the things that we've learned from
the previous couple times we've played
them, see what they're about um over
this last month since we've seen them,
and and let's go swing and let's be at
our best. let's find a way in those
three and a half hour windows to have
every single day leading up to that
moment give ourselves a chance to, you
know, to go do what we're capable of and
play better collectively. I thought we
played really well in certain phases.
Um, you know, and and and you guys, you
have heard you've heard me say it
tonight, you know, I'll be better for
us, we'll be better, but uh grateful for
the opportunity for sure.
>> Devonte across the field when Devonte
barely tow drags to bring it in.
>> Unbelievable. you know, well, I was
waiting to see if it was confirmed or
not cuz then we were trying to jump the
ball and they stand over it and, you
know, I'm getting a lot of mixed signals
on whether it was in or not. So, I'm not
sure if I got a second and 10 or a first
intent call and felt like an eternity
until they told me the damn thing was a
catch, but it was a great play by
Devonte.
>> Sean, that quarterback just hasn't
turned the ball over a lot this year.
Felt like you guys just didn't want to
let Kel beat you.
>> Yeah. And
>> how impressed are you with the defensive
performance?
>> I I'm so impressed. They carried the way
tonight and and they had a great week of
prep. Thought they had a great look in
their eye. Um Caleb made his plays. We
knew how dangerous he was, you know,
tactically, you know, schematically and
personnel-wise. They put a lot of
pressure on you and he certainly made
some great plays with his legs, but what
I was so impressed with in these
elements, our guys to be able to catch
the ball. I mean, that's a great
interception Cam Curl made. Um the Kobe
makes his plays and so I was really
pleased, Stacy, with the job that our
defense did. they deserve. I mean, it's
it's a game ball worthy performance for
the whole group and it's why we're
advancing to the NFC Championship.
>> Sorry.
>> How much does the experience you have,
whether it's Matthew, Devonte, Huga,
that that these guys have been here when
you're in elements like this and when
you're in a scenario?
>> I think it's big. You know, I I thought
we were at our best in the most
important moments. And I think whether
you're talking about the weather or just
big games, you could feel those guys
shine the brightest at the most
important moments. And I thought that's
what Matthew did when he had to um
there's some things that you know both
he and I I know we'll both be better
next week or we've got to be able to be
better if we expect to advance. But uh I
thought those guys that you mentioned
and then the players that I've
highlighted defensively. I thought you
know our front did a great job of being
able to apply pressure and then Caleb
made some of his plays. But I couldn't
be more impressed with just the overall
group effort from our defense and then
those guys you mentioned in the crunch
time moments. Okay. Thank you guys.
over time.
>> Um, shoot, I was confident. Um, he's
done it every time we've asked him. Um,
he stepped up and made kicks. He doesn't
practice all the time. He's consistent.
He's a gamer. So, uh, I just knew his
blood pressure be low. He'd be ready to
rock and roll. And I just great
operation, great snap, good hold. Those
were not easy conditions to do any of
that kind of stuff in. And then
obviously a great [clears throat] kick
there to uh to win it for us. What was
your what was your blood pressure like
in overtime? [clears throat]
>> Pretty steady. Um, you know, obviously
that first drive, um, wish I would have
done something there on that third down
to, you know, get us into a better one.
Um, that first, you know, first drive we
had in overtime. Obviously, our defense,
unbelievable play by Cam Curl getting
the pick. Our defense played outstanding
all night and then, uh, you know, we had
the opportunity to go down drive drive
down and and, uh, you know, give us a
chance to get in range or or, uh, score
a touchdown and and we were able to do
it. What did uh coach McVey tell you
during the timeout? He said he told us
he changed the play.
>> Yeah.
>> Before Pukas.
>> Yeah, we flipped it. Um flipped it. Had
a had a different play in there. He
asked me if I like the one that we ended
up running. I said, "Hell yeah, I love
that one." And um it was it was a great
call. Great feel by him to kind of bang
a timeout on the first one. Didn't have
a great look to what we wanted to do. Um
you know, and uh just great feel by him
on the sideline getting that done and
giving me a good play. And then
obviously Puka did a nice job after the
catch. Did you have any feel? I mean,
what was I know you said your finger was
fine and everything. Conditions were
kind of crazy.
>> Yeah.
>> Did you ever feel like you had a good
feel?
>> No, I I definitely, you know, didn't get
into a great rhythm today. There's no
question about that. Um, you know, had
some opportunities in the past game. Um,
you know, just some some things that
made it tough. Obviously, uh, I can be
better. Um, but, you know, playoff
football is about winning the football
game. Um, played great through for a
bunch of yards last year in the snow and
and we lost. So that sucks. So I'm
uh I'm happy to have uh played a little
bit uh worse today and going home with a
win. So we'll take that.
>> A week ago, you ripped their hearts out,
so to speak.
>> Yeah.
>> When you [clears throat and cough] when
Cam Curl got the interception.
>> Yep.
>> Were you in a similar mindset?
>> Yeah, absolutely. I looked right at
Shawn. He looked at me and was like, and
I'm like, here we go. And uh that's
that's what it's all about. What an
unbelievable, you know, job by, again,
like I said, by our defense today
getting us the ball over and over again,
whether it be fourth down stops or
turnovers. They were they were clutch
and timely. Um, and that's what it takes
to win in the playoffs. You know,
sometimes offense going to go out and
have a great day and find a way to win
it. Um, sometimes defense going to go
out there and have a day like they did
today and and keep us in it for as long
as they did and then make the play at
the end to get us the ball back. So,
it's a team effort. We got a resilient
group. Love being a part of it. Um,
obviously things we can do better. Um
but we found a way to win the football
game and and uh you know in January and
February that's what matters.
>> Talk about when you um something
[clears throat] like that Caleb Williams
fourth down throw down to to send you
guys into overtime happens. Um what is
it about you and the team and kind of
pulling back the emotional uh rope and
getting getting the last words.
>> I mean to be honest with you that's
that's what football's all about.
whether you have a great play the play
before a bad play or I mean shoot I
thought that was a great play by our
defense just a better play by Caleb and
and uh was it Kmet that caught it? Yeah.
Um you know just a better play by those
two guys and that happens in football.
Um yeah is it a you know a huge moment
and you know a tough a tough thing at
the moment but yeah but you move on. You
know there's more football to play. Um
we got to go out there and make sure
that we do uh you know do the right
things after that and and we were able
to as a team. We're not talking about
[clears throat] the cold all week, but
did you know how much snow you guys were
going to get and that it would stick?
>> Uh, no. You know, I wasn't, you know,
paying too much attention to, you know,
what the actual weather was or what it
was going to be. Um, you know, once we
got out there, it was snowed pretty
consistently the entire game. It felt
like, I don't know, you guys probably
know better than me, but, um, yeah, I
mean, it was wasn't the easiest
conditions, um, you know, to throw and
catch the football. Um, but we found a
way.
>> What did you say in the huddle on that
last drive before that last drive in
overtime? Yeah, just I mean same thing I
always say, man, let's just go get some
points. You know, at that point all
that's all that mattered. Um could we
get three? Could we get seven? Didn't
matter. Let's go get some points. Um we
were able to get that done and and come
away with the win.
>> What was the process of trying to adjust
to some of those DB blitzes that they
were bringing?
>> Yeah. Um you know, uh there was some
some things we can do better. Um you
know, and I can communicate a little bit
better, I think. Um you know, to help
make sure that we're, you know, in the
right spot and our guys are going to the
right spot. Um but, you know, I got to
give Dennis Allen some credit. Did a
nice job, you know, mixing it up on us.
was able to kind of sniff some of them
out some of them out late. Um, even on
some run plays and and be able to get us
closed up edge-wise. Um, which was great
and and kept us moving. U, but yeah,
they did a nice job mixing up on us. Um,
tough environment to communicate in, but
I I obviously can do a better job of
making sure that we all know where we
need to go and and and execute that
stuff.
>> They're very young team. Go ahead.
>> I'm sorry.
>> They're a very young team, first year
head coach. You guys have obviously been
here, you and Sean together. How much
does that help you, especially late in
the game tonight?
>> I don't know. They've been pretty good
late in games, you know. Um, they're
they're a tough out. There's no question
about that. I thought, you know, Ben's
done a hell of a job this year.
Obviously, Caleb's played great. Um, you
know, and did again tonight, you know,
in some in some timely moments late in
the game. So, um, they're a tough out.
They're a really good football team.
Obviously, in this in this position, in
this game, the number two seed in our
conference for a reason. um and being
able to go on the road and get it done
was huge.
>> And Matthew, forgive me if you were
asked this before, walking in, I walked
in, but um that throw to Devonte on the
opposite sideline and making the catch.
Um can you take us through like some of
maybe the micro moments of that? Like
when do you feel him open and and
>> Yeah. Um you know, the play before, um
>> Hook ended up coming out for that play.
Um so Sean did a nice job of getting us
to a great call. um you know got got
Devonte uh you know involved on a on a
deep out route and uh Nan Wright sat all
over it and you know Tay ran a great
route but I mean just he was playing
aggressive in the moment playing the
conditions playing all of it you know
and um Tay did a great job of running
out of that break. I tried to put it to
a spot that I thought was a good one.
He's as long as it gets at corner so I
knew it was going to have to be outside
outside and uh so I put it into a spot
that gave us a chance and uh what a what
a hell of a catch. I mean, uh, to be
able to catch it, get both feet down
from my vantage point, like real time, I
was like, there's no way, you know, and,
uh, then you watch the screen and holy
cow, we got him down and, um, had
control. So, incredible play by Devonte.
Um, you know, definitely wish I could
have gotten him a little bit more
involved on some ones early, but man,
when we needed him in some clutch
moments, he was huge tonight
[clears throat]
against a team that you know so well,
they know you so well.
>> Yeah, I mean, it's a huge challenge. Um
it's a huge challenge uh to go play in
Seattle. Um we've done it once this year
and what a hell of a game that was. And
um you know, they got such great players
on their team. They're really well
coached. They're coming off an
unbelievable game, you know, yesterday.
So they got a ton of momentum. Um but
I'm I'm sure excited to be in this
opportunity and be in this situation to,
you know, go see what we're all about.
um can we go into their place, pro
arguably the toughest place to play in
the league, a team that's played uh
really good football all year and and
find a way to win it and uh you know
continue this journey because that's
what it's about at this point in the
year. Um can we find a way to to work
together for another week and and um you
know we have the opportunity now and
it's it's exciting.
>> Thanks.
>> Hey, so we got back